We call the Oregon meeting of the United States Council for every first time.
I think we call it one, two, three, five, three, three minutes.
In January, 19th, 2021, the Oregon meeting.
Second.
Hi.
Honourable.
Four gates.
All right.
Four.
Three mayors, nomination of Brian Eastett,
to complete the checks I'm never trying.
Replacing David Davis for award.
One.
Two.
Three.
Two, five.
Four.
Five.
Two, five.
Is that okay?
Five.
Four.
Two.
Two, five.
Four.
Five.
and the government.
And the government not many we received directly working directly.
And I will not be lonely received directly or indirectly.
And many or other valuable things.
And many of the other valuable things.
So the performance or not performance of any act for the release.
For the performance or not performance of any act or you.
Or take it to my office.
Other than the compensation allowed by the law.
Protecting my office.
I've heard of this part of our firm.
I've heard of some of our work firm.
That I have been fully discharged.
And I will be fully discharged.
According to the best of my ability.
The best of my ability.
The disease of my office during such time is I am a member.
During the duties of my office.
Just as time is I remember.
Of the my ability from so forth one.
Of the my ability to answer more points.
And the board of trustees.
Of the my ability.
Of the city of my office.
I'm six of them again, but let's get the first one to answer.
I'm going to be perfectly old.
Good evening.
I have to have this.
My name is very little.
I'm going to ask you the least.
My family might have become a big number of three.
Part of what I'm going to say to my family.
I have any videos to refer.
I'm going to want to raise.
You start with the question.
I'm going to state.
It is harder to power.
I'm going to start doing clean-ups.
I have to be included.
I'm going to do a few things such as the amount of height.
If I go to this moment, there are one cancels.
Two mattresses.
A lot of women share as well as like a little bit.
Rather than two, we can pick up a lot of things to do so.
Or without making this money.
But two of them are so easy to do.
They don't care.
And on the outside of the park.
One of these can sign off.
And the other side.
As I've mentioned, the nature of those use for fishing.
I'm going to do a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit.
So, then what else to wear in our chairs?
And we put double set on the whilst standing distance,
I don't know if we're in a fish hole,
but I'm out there holding it in the park.
I'm also like this that is so easy on what the amount of people
can to do for 20 years.
We have a big benefits for today.
As well as I work really well,
we have a small and comfortable understanding.
Thank you very much.
We're seven since the end of the staff are immediately
through one of the data through June.
From 11th, public hearing on submission,
we'll make a great application to the volunteers
and the recreational department vision of state parks.
We have just a...
Good evening, council.
So the parks department, the parks department
has put in a grant request
and this request is for an 80-20 grant.
And every award at the city will be responsible.
We're 20% of this grant and plants that are funded through in-kind services.
What this will be will be, we're calling it, this flash trail, and it'll be a walking trail located
on a barbecue where the flash pad is right now.
The city, Miami, the closest provided a pathway trail that will be approximately one mile
length and encompassed the Miami Route 66 flash pad, the Joe Pollock Sports Complex, and the
tennis sports slash skate park area.
The trail will be asphalted with limestone, base eight foot wide to the calling both walkers
and those for wheelchairs.
The trail will cross over the bridge that was put in place in 2020, and will just access
over the natural ditch that can hold water during every rain events.
The trail will be, well, last in a since walking cross, access to the areas mentioned
above the bridge that we're talking about right now, it doesn't have the railings on it
as we speak, but we're just waiting for the contractor to start, which is doing some other jobs right
now.
This week, the next, they'll start that project.
Bences, shade structures, vegetation, lighting, and signage from the place along the trail.
Other features may be added as funds allow it.
So as you can see right now, here is where the splash pad is.
This is the bridge that we were talking about.
What's going to be really nice about this is that this is really our only park from the parking
on to the restrooms in the railroad, that is ADA and wine.
So when this is, hopefully we're allowed this ramp, and it's completed, you'll be able to park here
and walk over the bridge and go throughout the park and around and use the restrooms in a wheelchair.
We're really excited about that point.
So we see here, here's the Joe Pollock, Ballfield, here's the tennis courts and the skate park.
So this is what, you'll have to forgive us a little bit on the computer in the lines.
It doesn't allow us to do incurring.
So what this is, here's the parking lot to the splash pad and the picture that we use.
It's an older one, so the splash pad isn't there, but it's located here.
You'll be able to come out of the parking lot, go across the bridge, or around the ballfield,
go around the tennis courts, the skate park, and turn back.
Of course, the track will be a little bit of a monkey as...
90 like this one is back over there and around we're thinking about putting a shake structure
somewhere back in here so you'll not only will use this parking but this as well we think
this will be a really neat walk to have it's one of our focus parks hopefully we will be successful
on the grant and we're just really excited for the opportunity it's one of one of the one
we'll have Mark who's around what it was nice about this too it ties in to our healthy community
again as well and we want to go really excited to the fact that this will be an all 88
is it going to be live all around oh yes you're planning on
I mean I know we just like 20% on matching but we have the idea
not this time it's run out of 150,000 dollar
grant that we will have
grant 30,000 dollar
that was a park park tour where they think about this
I have a talk to them about it
we both are making a surprise upon stuff
and knowing that I'm not very excited
it was normally way to get renovations from there before we could do that
this is just great formation yeah there is no match
yeah the application had to be turned in about the end of January
so we had to move before we had a chance to present a new park tour
which would be better
yeah it's one of the kinds of grants
sometimes you have to jump in there
like so we have it up
yeah sorry
you know what you think before you know yes or no on the grant
I'll get you done for a couple of months
I know that we'll turn it in and they figured a couple of months before they
even look at that
thank you
I'll stand here to come there
they have a question well some other
there is a public hearing
so you need to declare it as a public hearing
but as you both I think what I'm saying about this
grant is a public hearing
so you might have any questions on this
if it doesn't
let's walk you down
so there are any protection on expected additional water usage for
that
the way that grant we had in there is a question
water usage
gross water
And this is a trial and cell or a luxury curve.
I mean, just additional costs to the city
we'll have to pay for that on up the basis.
I know, I know now.
I'll make sure that.
I mean, yeah, I mean, there'll be lots.
We will hope to have power into the exchange
structure of just like we do at this flashback.
So yes, there will be a very, very big to the city.
And we can go bar high, get you something out there.
There's always a chance to have additional places.
Thank you.
I don't know.
This is something I'd like to say.
I don't know if you guys thought that enough.
I'd also like to say that to that chance.
OK.
I think you can still say, you can have the walk of night,
and feel like they're, you know, it can be long terms.
This is the district.
Thank you.
OK.
Yeah.
I can definitely bring it up in part four.
Any other questions for the committee?
OK.
Well, update on the current condition of the climate.
This will go just to take this one as well.
So we talked a few of a month ago about the liner
and the pool in the fourth condition.
And needed to be the river.
We're coming back to now to tell you what we found out about.
We haven't about a quarter of the liner pool already,
and it's been a lot harder to remove than what we initially thought.
The way they saw that liner is the glue.
The cleaner surface, the glue, at least the down,
they put a filled amount down, and then they
could glue on it, and then they put a PVC liner in.
And where the water didn't penetrate the liner,
it is like they just put it on.
So when we go to rip it in that, it is hanging on to the concrete.
So this is a picture of what, for those who can remember
back in 06, this is before they did the first liner installed.
And it still has that island out there.
So this is when they removed the liner, this is before they installed,
removed the island before they installed the new liner.
And this is kind of what we thought we might see.
And as you can see, just from the picture, it looks,
it leads, but it still looks decent.
So this is, when they did the ring model in 1977,
they rebuilt the curving for the side of the pool of all the way around.
And so this little blue tile, and put this red, this is the skimbed
of the water, this is where the water comes over,
and then the bridge washes down, and gets a refilled.
This is kind of what we thought we might see when.
and we pulled the liner.
This is what we found instead.
The concrete has deteriorated so bad,
and the glue still holding that when we ripped it up,
it is just falling apart all throughout.
I can see here, it's just coming off in chunks.
There's another area where it is just disintegrated.
Here's a portion of the side where it is just,
it is not exactly what we expected at all.
So, same kind of area, but you can see down through here,
and all the along for here.
Everywhere we've ripped off the liners is what we're seeing here.
So here's a corner of the edge.
You can tell right here,
concrete's pretty much returning back to aggregate.
It just crumbles in your hand, cracks all the way through.
So at this point, we have determined that what we thought would you go back
and with outline, and do it in cheaper repair,
it's not feasible.
We are going to have to go back to the line.
We talked to a concrete expert,
and we're pretty much going to have to cut this out all the way around
and rebuild that curving in order to support the liner.
As of right now, we put out the lid,
getting it together for the liner.
But we still have not gotten permission from the state
to allow us to put a new liner back.
Speaking with them, they're pretty buzzing with that.
Being able to, but it's right now,
we still have not gotten the consent to be able to do it.
But we're going to make sure we get our dogs on the road.
So when we do, get that curving which we expect to get,
that we can start to receive.
So these are just ballpark figures of what we know right now.
From estimates, a new pool liner is going to be around 220,
give or take.
The sand in the three filters that we have.
It's been over 10 years since it've been looked at and replaced.
If we have to replace the sand,
and if there's repairs to it, they're looked around 10,000.
Speaking with some others, we might not have to do that.
We're going to find out.
We looked at sandblasting and painting,
just a structure of the slide.
The slide was still in a warranty last year
that the guys were sliding apart of it.
And if that repair holds up,
we'll think that we can do the cheaper with just sandblasting
the structure itself and painting,
and not testing the slide.
We have one estimate for that.
9700 and then the support names that were underneath the restroom area would think we can
sandblast and think those we feel around 5,000. So to kind of sum up where we're at, we know
that we're going to have to go back and go on. We're still waiting for a stay approval which we
feel we'll get and that point where the process of making up big practices in that for a place
in the box. Thank you for taking a look at the bits are out for the comfort to get in the
unit. Yes, well, which means if that's not included in this, it's gonna be a different
day. We think around 25,000. With the area of the museum with the plug, how long would this
work? Well, a line of music 10 to 15 years. Our last line did not hold up as well because it
is damaged during the storm. So we're hoping in 10 to 15 years without damage. But where
this was, where the coolest located, we're always susceptible to flood. One flood of times,
you know, the debris comes within it. There's always such a chance. So, but without
water, we don't have a hole. The longer it's, the 10 year warranty, then it does not cover
the actual disaster. So we don't have any gloves and we don't have any alternatives about the
way. We had to take a year warranty on the line. So we can fix it. But as soon as we have
a flood that packs up, we get a pool that does away with that one. So the liner was installed
in 2005. We had the flood in 2007. We had some storms right after that. So that kind of pointed
that more to you, due to the natural disasters that we're on. So we'll be glad to have you
there since. We're coming out, I mean, we're working on doing it to be someone who
will have a lot of time to do the disaster. So maybe get some of that money and get the back
of what we've prepared. So I'll get it with concrete prepared, Dr. Ballpark, use it at the back.
Yes, or more?
Just in the veins under the back of the rest rooms, if I remember correctly, we would look at the
slides, maybe we could really get scared.
They did, but we had to look at it. It's mainly surface and we give it the same last in the panoramic
and then...
That's going to make them stable.
That will make them the last of the veins we can get the last of the long hands, the pool.
We have to realize that the pool is 80 years old. It does have a shelf like a bench building.
So, I was talking about, it's worth a grantment because that's how we already have it.
That's basically going to be like, I mean, you don't have to make it.
We have not been nominated one with 80% of the things?
Yeah.
And we have not got that money in.
But they just want us to get in.
Yes, it hasn't been nominated.
It's been some days, but we could go all the way to the government.
We're went out to that.
But that has to go to the pool.
Correct.
But there's one other aspect that I came in there that you need to keep in mind.
Two years ago, I think, was being made of something that we're planning for.
Which applies to the city, just as well as it does.
The homeowner is right there.
And there's a limitation as to how much money you can put into the parent.
A structure, such as pool, that is in and of both life.
Sounds like we're getting somewhat close to that amount.
But we can't see 50% of the value of the property or the repairs.
50% of the repairs.
What do you want to do?
We try to get the full amount of look at it and give us a cost.
And they say the dues was age and size.
They don't have any words to be used with confidence to see what it would be clear.
So we don't know about it.
It's seven minutes.
So that period, if we're getting a hundred and five, it has to be filled with pools.
And so that's actually the picture pool.
And for the final place, we can't fix it again.
Perhaps the preliminary that we've received from the state,
that this would be a one-time variance if they allow it at all.
They will allow it.
So we can essentially get this variance.
We have 10 years to come up with a plan for the pool.
We have a hundred and nine feet in the initials.
So if you just think about it, we have one nine to the end.
We can't.
Plus the one in the back of the pool.
Plus the only bond.
So the funding we should have had to be able to take care of if everything goes well.
We've got to have you all going back through what the incident is that.
How do we get it?
If I'm trying.
So get that all that bonus.
Just like the leader.
I submitted a flood.
I'm going to ask you the code source.
I'm going to give you the dollar.
So add it back.
No.
Go there, so you'll come back to this way.
So yes.
Yes.
Hopefully, hopefully we'll hear it back from the states in.
And, as soon as we get our package ready, we'll send that out.
And we should be getting a bit more in contact with a couple of environments
so I think getting it back won't be that difficult.
That's the caveat that we were not on a sincere on that.
And we are writing out writing the rest, not only on time.
Pretty quick, isn't it?
We're going to go ahead and go out to the end of the ladder.
Hopefully we'll come back up to the end of the state.
You just superb.
The next time you see us, we'll come back to an action.
And then we'll have dates and numbers of what's going to take to get that.
We'll be getting reinforcements.
We've got cane, marriage, nomination.
Take the loose.
Considerment is over there.
Three choice.
I don't think they're going to be.
The 14, the new business has a residence.
It's a close of 50, 15, stay at Fortress.
16, mayor.
A gentle community, no business.
I have the fourth day to let those separate that thing.
So at the given moment.
I think I'm going to make sure that we get a list of all.
All right.
Thank you very much.
The question is, what's more about your reserves?
I thought a lot about that.
I'm going to go back and ask you a little bit about Berkeley.
I'm going to speak and you mentioned that too.
Trash, that's just, that's something that's, something that's,
something we need to, I mean, I think it's a great thing.
Everything we're doing.
As if we could be a system that way,
and hopefully we can probably go to Berkeley and also think that we're good.
I already did that Mr. Roberts.
Okay.
I'll take care of that.
I'm not sure.
If we, I think, parts of the level.
that we fight for the days of being sent down in our parts for the most.
It's not only a phenomenon, it's not a topic.
17 city managers, communications and anything.
And anything?
So, what?
It's working.
We have a side of the building.